ANKITA GUPTA



ankitanavrtan@gmail.com

17017594747, 8791516090



linkedin.com/in/ankita-gupta-b27963111

Summary

I have a total Experience is 4.9 years and In UI designing is 3.8 years.

5 months of experience in Expires Manpower, and the client was TCS.

3.3 years of Experience as a Software Developer of Government Solution Applications at AKIKO SHERMAN INFOTECH and the client was the Indian Council for Cultural Relations (ICCR) New Delhi.

8 months Experience in ICCS as a Technical Assistance. 4 Months Experience in Vertex as a Technical Assistance.

Skills

Adobe Photoshop • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Bootstrap • ¡Query UI • JavaScript • Figma (Software) • Wire framing • Balsamic • Prototyping• Creative Designing • Usability • Design Systems • Usability Testing

Portfolio Website Link

https://github.com/Ankita2102/AnkitaFolio

Experience

User Interface Designer

Experis

Sep 2022 - Jan 2023 (5 months)

September 2022-Febuary 2023

Client - Tata Consultancy Services

Domain-India Team Size: 8 Roles: UI Designer

Project: Application Name- AXA Monitoring

Description: AXA Monitoring is a web Application, used in Hong Kong country, where we receive tickets and resolve them within a given timeline. And resolve a Designing issue of the application.

ROLES & RESPONSIBILITIES

- 1. Implement responsible web design principles to ensure that our company website renders well Across multiple devices.
- 2. Design a framework for creating user apps that grows with the needs of the company Monitor website performance, watch for traffic drops related to site usability problems and rectify the
- 3. Review app and feature coding and plan future website upgrades with the development team.
- 4. Assist in the development of applications and features that will be put on the website and in internal functions as well.

Team Size: 8:

Project: Application Name- AXA Monitoring

Description: AXA Monitoring is a web Application, used in Hong Kong country, where we receive tickets and resolve them within a given timeline. And resolve a Designing issue of the application



Akiko Sherman InfoTech

Jan 2019 - Mar 2022 (3 years 3 months)

Domain: E-Governance

Testing Team Size: 6 - 8; Project 1: DBT (Direct Benefit Transfer)

Description:

DBT Application developed with the aim of reforming Government delivery system by re-

Engineering the existing process in welfare schemes for simpler And faster flow of ----information/funds and to ensure accurate targeting of the beneficiaries, de-duplication and reduction of fraud Direct Benefit Transfer (DBT); E-Office (Electronic office)

Description:

The introduction of e-office improved accuracy and efficiency of organizations and Thereby improved their level of service, while theoretically lowering costs and drastically Reducing the consumption of paper. Many documents are still being printed out and circulated on paper, however, especially those that require signatures or other legal formalities.

Project 3: ICCR Website (Indian Council for Cultural Relations)

Description:

Handling the all Front-End Technical duties in website of ICCR.URL:

www.iccr.gov.in

Project 4: Handle all Virtual Meetings and Events.

Description: iccr.webex.com

Technical Assistant

ICCS

Feb 2018 - Dec 2018 (11 months)

Handle all the Technical Issues in Project.

Vertex Technical Associate

Vertex Group May 2017 - September 2017 (5 months)

Handle all the Technical Issues in Project.

Education



B.Tech 2012 - 2016



12th

2011 - 2012

UP Board

10th

2009 - 2010